Guide to the SAC Sudiorecordings
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
SAC audiorecordings
1975
SC1135
Stanford University
0.5 Linear feet (12 audiocassettes)
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Access Terms
Bach, Lee.; Bernstein, Barton.; Dornbusch, Sanford M.; Gurley, Jack.; Audiotapes.; Humanities--United States.
Collection Contents
- Audiorecordings
  - Lecture #7: Barton Bernstein, "Hiroshima Reconsidered", 1975 Jul 29; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Lecture #8: Barton Bernstein, "Vietnam Ain't No Edsel", 1975 Jul 29; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Lecture #11: Jack Gurley, "Up & Down: Inflation & Unemployment", 1975 Jul 31; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Lecture #11: Jack Gurley, "Up & Down: Inflation & Unemployment"; Lecture #12: Sanford Dornbusch, "Down & Out", 1975 Jul 31; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Lecture #12: Sanford Dornbusch, "Down & Out", 1975 Jul 31; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Lee Bach, "The State of the Economy & the American Dream", 1975 Aug 1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Lecture #13: Sanford Dornbusch, "Kidding the Kids", 1975 Aug 1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Lecture #13: Sanford Dornbusch, "Kidding the Kids", 1975 Aug 1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Lecture #15: Barton Bernstein, 1975 Aug 2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Lecture #15: Barton Bernstein, 1975 Aug 2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Panel discussion: Pearson, Gurley, Bernstein, Dornbusch, 1975 Aug 2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)